devasp.com 2017-06-19

# Privacy Policy - DevASP

DevASP.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. 

The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information DevASP.com may gather about individuals who visit its Web site, how that information is used, and DevASP.com’s disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to DevASP.com’s Web site and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links. 

**Site Usage Information**  
DevASP.com gathers “site usage” information from all visitors to the DevASP.com Web site. Such data is used in the aggregate, to help determine general usage patterns and fine tune layout in order to ensure that our site is as useful and enjoyable as possible. This “site usage” and statistical information may be made public information at DevASP.com’s discretion.

**Use of Cookies**  
When you view our Web site, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a ‘Cookie’ and will help us in many ways. For example, Cookies allow us to tailor our Web site to better match your interests and preferences and optionally provide automatic member login. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

**Individual User Information**  
DevASP.com will collect personal information if you choose to become a DevASP.com member. The personal information we collect includes your name, e-mail, and/or work phone, work or home address, company or organization name. We do not share neither e-mail addresses nor individually identifiable information with any third parties.

**Disclosure**  
DevASP.com reserves the right to access and disclose individually identifiable information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself or its users. Where practical, DevASP.com will attempt to obtain the prior consent of the individual prior to disclosing individually identifiable information. As mentioned above, we reserve the right to share aggregated “site usage” information with third parties. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or believe that we have not adhered to the guidelines set forth above, please [contact us](http://www.devasp.com/contact/). 

Thank you.
